<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE locale SYSTEM "../../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/locale.dtd">

<!--
  * plugins/generic/fidusWriter/locale/en_US/locale.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2013 Simon Fraser University Library
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2013 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Localization strings
  -->
 
<locale name="en_US" full_name="U.S. English">
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.name">FidusWriter Plugin</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.description"><![CDATA[This plugin permits the integration of <a href="http://www.fiduswriter.org">FidusWriter</a> as a content editor for submission documents.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.manager.settings">Settings</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.manager.fidusWriterSettings">FidusWriter Settings</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.manager.settings.description">Use the following form to configure your OJS installation with the details of a FidusWriter installation to which OJS can delegate document creation and editing processes.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.manager.settings.apiUrl">API URL</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.manager.settings.apiUrlInstructions">The API URL is the base URL that OJS will use to interact with FidusWriter.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.manager.settings.apiUrlRequired">You must enter a valid API URL.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.manager.settings.apiKeyRequired">You must enter a valid API key.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.manager.settings.apiKey">API key</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.manager.settings.apiKeyNotValidated">The specified API URL and key could not be validated. Please double-check both values.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.redirect">Redirect</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.redirect.description">You are about to be redirected to FidusWriter, an external tool that can be used to compose and edit scholarly content. Please note that although FidusWriter has the ability to save your document back to this journal, it may be hosted on a different server. When you are finished, you will be directed back here to continue the submission process.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.revise">Revise</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.fidusWriter.revise.description">Submissions will be revised using FidusWriter, an external tool that can be used to compose and edit scholarly content. Please note that although FidusWriter has the ability to save your document back to this journal, it may be hosted on a different server. When you are finished, you will be directed back here.</message>
</locale>
